Ivona Josipovic

Front-end developer

(+46)70 006 68 48



ABOUT ME

A hard-working and dynamic developer with four years of experience as a group manager and coordinator. Regular tinkering with my ten-year-old blog was the starting point for an initial appreciation that later became a total embrace of Frontend development and Javascript in particular.

SKILLS

HTML5, CSS, JavaScript (ES6+), TypeScript Frameworks: React, Vue Node.js, Express, MongoDB, Axios, RESTful API, Vite Other: SCSS/Sass, Tailwind, Netlify, GitHub, Azure DevOps, ClickUp, Trello, WordPress

EDUCATION

Lexicon Stockholm (2022/2023)

Frontend development full-time course:

- Responsive web development with **HTML5 & CSS**
- Frontend programming in **Javascript** with **React** and **Vue** as frameworks
 - Backend programming in Node.js with Express
 - Databases: MongoDB

Istituto Europeo di Design *Milan, Italy* (2012) Master's degree in communication, PR and styling

Faculty for Design Belgrade, Serbia (2010) Bachelor's Degree in Fashion Design

CERTIFICATES







WORK HISTORY

Frontend developer Intern

Sublime - March to June 2023

Helped the Sublime team build new features, solve bugs and issues that appear, and convert design mockups into seamless frontend components. Focused on implementing responsive web solutions with HTML, SASS, and JS.

Sales Coordinator

Sisu Net AB - March 2020 to July 2022
Responsible for coordinating B2B flows (sales, inventory, financing) from order placement till delivery. Worked hand-in-hand with the sales force for support and active customer retention.

Manager

Stockholm Stad - November 2018 to March 2020
Managed a facility under the City of Stockholm that
offered childcare to families with unusual working hours.
Responsible for scheduling, purchasing, inventory
management, and maintaining good relationships
between childcare recipients and providers.

Marketing strategist focusing on social media

Boom Watches - February to September 2018
Managed all social media channels for Boom Watches, analyzing the impact of campaigns and social media strategies on sales. Responsible for various collaborations with social media influencers. Worked closely with our creators in an effort to strengthen the brand

Freelance Copywriter / Writer

Nelly.com, Grazia, Harper's Bazaar - 2012 to 2018 Freelance contributor for various magazines and online publications. Freelancing helped me improve my time management and communication skills and made me a better team player.

LANGUAGES

Swedish, English (advanced), Serbian (mother tongue), Italian (intermediate), Spanish, French (beginner)